{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724141355","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724141355"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724183334","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724183334"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b505b9b0-5bf4-4d2b-ab8b-6d77aa54dde1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724185642","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724185641"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b505b9b0-5bf4-4d2b-ab8b-6d77aa54dde1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724220675","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724220675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b505b9b0-5bf4-4d2b-ab8b-6d77aa54dde1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724220746","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724220746"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b505b9b0-5bf4-4d2b-ab8b-6d77aa54dde1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724238303","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724238303"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b505b9b0-5bf4-4d2b-ab8b-6d77aa54dde1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724238365","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724238365"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" ea019b8c-533f-4a43-8746-491ec1154ebd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724257889","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724257888"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_i_y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724264560","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724264560"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_a_f"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724271212","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724271212"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_u_z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724277872","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724277872"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_f_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724284457","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724284457"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_i_v"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724291877","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724291877"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_i_v"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724298494","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724298494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_p_s"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724305077","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724305076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_z_f"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724312498","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724312498"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_z_f"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724322732","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724322732"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_z_f"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724328925","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724328924"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_g_f"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724331498","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724331498"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_d_g_f"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724343493","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724343492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 8fdbbb51-022f-4ede-887a-13ccdd382dd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_d_g_f"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724349207","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724349207"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b209858b-91cf-4fb2-bbe6-df19b6553212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724361585","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724361584"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b209858b-91cf-4fb2-bbe6-df19b6553212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724364476","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724364476"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b209858b-91cf-4fb2-bbe6-df19b6553212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724364603","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724364603"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b209858b-91cf-4fb2-bbe6-df19b6553212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724373576","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724373576"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_r-f-l"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724380527","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724380527"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_s-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724388246","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724388246"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_w-ch-f"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724391388","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724391388"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-ch-g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724396493","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724396492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-ch-g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724399560","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724399560"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-s-d"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724402692","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724402691"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_v-z-f"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724408215","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724408215"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_v-z-f"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724413808","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724413808"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_k-f-l"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724417003","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724417003"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-l-ch"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724420239","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724420239"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_b-f-e"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724423595","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724423595"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_l-f-w"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724429362","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724429361"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 1d45d9d8-a356-48b5-a4a1-107a7ec5464b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_f_l-f-w"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724456050","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724456049"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 235a75ca-5bd7-41e2-9dc7-8bf35d616f7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724481211","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724481211"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 235a75ca-5bd7-41e2-9dc7-8bf35d616f7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724500234","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724500233"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 235a75ca-5bd7-41e2-9dc7-8bf35d616f7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724514060","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724514060"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 235a75ca-5bd7-41e2-9dc7-8bf35d616f7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724514123","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724514123"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 235a75ca-5bd7-41e2-9dc7-8bf35d616f7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724541929","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724541929"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724565446","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724565446"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724584638","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724584638"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724606980","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724606980"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724626087","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724626086"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724628412","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724628412"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724650611","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724650611"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_11"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724670254","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724670254"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724691374","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724691372"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724691492","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724691492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724698222","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724698221"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724703632","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724703631"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724708385","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724708385"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" b482e330-ccfb-4a8f-8278-e56b916a4451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724736694","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724736693"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_bado-mno-mwalimu-mwenye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" mno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724754377","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724754377"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_wao-bado-vya-mno"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" mno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724771748","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724771748"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_jambo-mno-bado-kamba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" mno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724796637","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724796637"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zaidi_kuku-mara-zaidi-baada"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" zaidi"," userResponse":" zaidi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724818029","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724818029"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sana_wakati-sana-nyumbani-kwamba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" sana"," userResponse":" sana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724841086","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724841086"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlango_bado-mtoto-kijiji-mlango"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mlango"," userResponse":" mlango"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724859368","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724859368"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sana_lakini-mama-sana-kwenda"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" sana"," userResponse":" sana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724879547","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724879547"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_kamba-mno-njiani-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" kubwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724882212","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724882212"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_kamba-mno-njiani-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" mno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724910690","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724910690"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_mno-zao-njiani-nina"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" mno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724928412","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724928411"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mno_mno-zao-njiani-nina"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724928568","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724928568"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724934015","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724934015"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::1..4.SD_OFF1_DES.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724939400","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724939399"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724945364","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724945363"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724951711","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724951711"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724957190","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724957189"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724962031","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724962031"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724966633","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724966632"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" e9bd5a39-3516-4000-998b-752ec681b727"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724980827","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724980825"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HI"," userResponse":" HI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724981110","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724981109"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724981927","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724981926"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724982031","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724982031"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724982882","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724982882"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724983334","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724983333"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724984372","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724984371"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724985521","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724985521"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724985890","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724985890"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724986492","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724986491"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724987381","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724987381"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724990620","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724990618"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724991281","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724991281"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724991847","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724991847"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724992219","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724992218"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724993102","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724993101"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724993904","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724993903"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724994490","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724994489"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724995122","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724995122"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724995913","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724995913"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724996314","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724996314"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724997151","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724997151"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724997688","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724997687"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724998583","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724998583"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543724999442","data":{"timestamp":" 1543724999442"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725002585","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725002584"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIYEFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725003302","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725003302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725004264","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725004264"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725004995","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725004995"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725005681","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725005681"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725006094","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725006093"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725006332","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725006331"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725006787","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725006787"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKA"," userResponse":" MWAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725007499","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725007499"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725010100","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725010099"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725011153","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725011151"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEBEBWA"," userResponse":" AMEBEBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725011973","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725011973"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725012497","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725012496"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725012663","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725012663"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725013283","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725013282"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725014066","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725014065"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725017313","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725017313"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725017601","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725017601"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725018569","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725018568"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725019256","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725019256"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725020780","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725020780"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" WALIMWONEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725021832","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725021831"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725022167","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725022167"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" HURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725023148","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725023148"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725025885","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725025884"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725027019","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725027018"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEKONDA"," userResponse":" AMEKONDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725027259","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725027259"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725027721","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725027721"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725028533","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725028533"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725031781","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725031781"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725032209","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725032209"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725032811","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725032810"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725033782","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725033781"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725034760","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725034760"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725035381","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725035381"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725035879","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725035878"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725036521","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725036521"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFYA"," userResponse":" AFYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725039318","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725039318"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725040091","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725040091"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725040346","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725040346"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725041054","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725041053"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725041918","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725041918"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725042741","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725042741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725043651","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725043651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725046697","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725046697"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725047411","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725047411"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725048025","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725048024"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725048463","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725048463"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725048620","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725048619"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725049090","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725049090"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725049904","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725049904"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725051109","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725051108"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725051363","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725051363"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITUA"," userResponse":" ILITUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725052554","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725052554"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725052617","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725052617"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725053450","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725053449"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725056631","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725056630"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725056911","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725056911"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725057833","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725057832"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725058491","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725058489"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725060129","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725060129"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" WALIHARAKISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725060671","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725060671"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725061196","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725061196"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725063711","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725063710"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725063814","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725063813"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725064824","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725064824"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725065891","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725065890"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725066073","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725066073"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725066663","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725066663"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725067660","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725067657"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUNGWA"," userResponse":" ALIFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725068379","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725068379"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725069033","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725069033"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725069827","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725069827"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725072636","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725072636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725073309","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725073308"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIWA"," userResponse":" NDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725074370","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725074369"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725075093","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725075093"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725076051","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725076051"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725078711","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725078710"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725078919","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725078918"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725079510","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725079510"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725079679","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725079678"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725080169","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725080169"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725080736","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725080736"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725083498","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725083498"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725084383","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725084382"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMLISHA"," userResponse":" ALIMLISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725084984","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725084984"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIWA"," userResponse":" NDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725085734","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725085734"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725086323","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725086322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725089412","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725089412"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATIMA"," userResponse":" YATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725089584","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725089584"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725090185","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725090185"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725091049","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725091049"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725091206","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725091206"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725092218","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725092217"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725092797","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725092797"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALEA"," userResponse":" MALEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725095787","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725095787"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKISHWA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKISHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725096502","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725096501"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725097490","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725097489"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725097999","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725097998"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725098765","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725098764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBWA"," userResponse":" KUBEBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725099291","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725099291"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725099903","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725099903"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TREKTA"," userResponse":" TREKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725100727","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725100726"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725103360","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725103359"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725103601","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725103601"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725104209","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725104208"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725104373","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725104373"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725104987","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725104987"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEZI"," userResponse":" MIEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725105586","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725105586"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725108439","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725108438"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALEA"," userResponse":" MALEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725109511","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725109511"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725110269","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725110269"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFARU"," userResponse":" KIFARU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725112979","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725112979"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725113604","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725113603"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725113782","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725113782"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725114490","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725114489"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725114785","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725114785"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725115537","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725115537"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENKARE"," userResponse":" ENKARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725116832","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725116831"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYE"," userResponse":" AMBAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725117448","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725117448"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725118052","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725118052"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" NYATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725118809","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725118808"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725121484","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725121484"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725122297","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725122296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725123089","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725123088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725123833","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725123833"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725126823","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725126822"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725127598","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725127597"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725128856","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725128855"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725129315","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725129315"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725130331","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725130331"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMSHWA"," userResponse":" ALIAMSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725130869","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725130869"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725131519","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725131518"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725131892","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725131891"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725132529","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725132529"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBIA"," userResponse":" AMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725135724","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725135723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBIA"," userResponse":" AMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725136483","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725136482"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725136721","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725136721"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725137276","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725137275"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725137475","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725137474"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725138098","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725138098"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEZI"," userResponse":" MIEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725138812","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725138811"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITANO"," userResponse":" MITANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725141483","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725141482"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHISI"," userResponse":" ALIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725142163","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725142163"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725142502","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725142502"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725143509","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725143508"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHOVU"," userResponse":" UCHOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725144356","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725144356"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725144602","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725144598"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725145144","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725145143"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725146156","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725146155"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725148637","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725148637"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725149256","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725149256"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725149442","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725149442"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725150006","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725150005"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725150464","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725150463"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725150889","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725150888"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725152004","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725152004"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725153222","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725153221"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIISHIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725153819","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725153818"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725154293","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725154292"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725155062","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725155061"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725155868","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725155868"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLISHA"," userResponse":" KUMLISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725158990","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725158990"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPACHA"," userResponse":" MAPACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725159625","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725159625"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABEI"," userResponse":" ABEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725159854","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725159854"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725160558","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725160557"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOIT"," userResponse":" MOIT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725161682","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725161681"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725162836","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725162836"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725162900","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725162900"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725163499","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725163499"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725164302","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725164302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725167002","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725167001"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725168011","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725168011"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEZALIWA"," userResponse":" WAMEZALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725168522","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725168521"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725168793","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725168793"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHACHE"," userResponse":" CHACHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725169097","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725169097"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725171880","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725171880"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725173059","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725173059"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAGONJWA"," userResponse":" WAGONJWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725173630","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725173629"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725176582","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725176582"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725177264","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725177263"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725178927","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725178927"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" ALIHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725180050","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725180050"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725180871","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725180870"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABEI"," userResponse":" ABEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725181849","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725181849"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAGA"," userResponse":" ALIAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725182555","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725182555"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" DUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725183327","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725183326"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725183952","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725183952"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725184659","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725184659"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725184911","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725184911"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725185566","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725185565"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725186053","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725186052"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725187065","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725187065"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725189662","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725189662"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725190366","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725190365"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725190578","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725190578"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725191483","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725191483"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725192107","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725192106"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725193633","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725193633"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWOKOA"," userResponse":" WALIMWOKOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725194293","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725194293"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOIT"," userResponse":" MOIT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725197693","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725197692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725197934","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725197933"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725198456","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725198455"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725199182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725199182"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725199646","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725199646"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725199806","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725199805"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725200350","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725200350"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725201289","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725201289"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725202224","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725202223"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725203083","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725203082"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOPI"," userResponse":" KOPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725204155","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725204153"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KEPI"," userResponse":" KEPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725204807","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725204806"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725205568","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725205568"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KEJI"," userResponse":" KEJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725208210","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725208210"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725209166","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725209165"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASIMBA"," userResponse":" WANASIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725210091","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725210091"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725210334","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725210333"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725210871","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725210871"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725211092","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725211092"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725211507","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725211507"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725211964","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725211963"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725214678","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725214676"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHISI"," userResponse":" WALIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725215104","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725215104"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" KIU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725215706","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725215705"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725216809","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725216809"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725220235","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725220234"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725220659","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725220659"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725221480","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725221479"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725222059","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725222059"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725223385","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725223385"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWAPENDA"," userResponse":" WALIWAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725223998","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725223998"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725224489","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725224489"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725225291","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725225291"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725225686","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725225685"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725226587","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725226586"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATUKUTU"," userResponse":" WATUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725229501","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725229500"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" MTUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725230078","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725230077"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725230692","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725230691"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725231224","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725231224"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOBOLIA"," userResponse":" LOBOLIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725233984","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725233984"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOBOLIA"," userResponse":" LOBOLIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725234878","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725234878"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725235621","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725235621"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFICHA"," userResponse":" KUFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725236415","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725236415"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWANI"," userResponse":" MIWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725236480","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725236480"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725237143","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725237142"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725240147","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725240147"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725240741","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725240741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725241393","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725241393"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725242237","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725242237"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725243310","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725243310"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAFANYA"," userResponse":" WANAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725244053","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725244053"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725245148","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725245148"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWATUNZA"," userResponse":" KUWATUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725245822","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725245822"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725246376","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725246375"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725247080","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725247080"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725250039","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725250039"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANATUMAI"," userResponse":" WANATUMAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725250344","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725250344"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725250777","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725250777"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725251341","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725251341"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725252495","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725252495"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725252999","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725252999"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725254122","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725254121"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATAWEZA"," userResponse":" WATAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725255405","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725255405"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITEGEMEA"," userResponse":" KUJITEGEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725256389","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725256389"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" WENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725256823","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725256823"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725257268","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725257268"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725259898","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725259898"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725261020","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725261020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATAWEZA"," userResponse":" WATAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725261613","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725261613"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725262436","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725262436"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PORINI"," userResponse":" PORINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725265128","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725265128"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725265691","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725265691"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725266404","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725266404"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725266749","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725266749"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725266984","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725266983"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725267987","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725267987"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGAPI"," userResponse":" WANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725270403","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725270402"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOMA"," userResponse":" SOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725270994","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725270994"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725271923","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725271923"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725272733","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725272733"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725273316","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725273316"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJIBU"," userResponse":" UJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725273991","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725273991"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725274286","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725274286"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725313879","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725313879"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725313959","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725313959"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725319684","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725319684"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725327168","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725327168"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2s.AV.mc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725331531","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725331531"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725335973","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725335972"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" dbb61c22-4749-4fb8-8184-a05beeff6212"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725344907","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725344906"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725345442","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725345442"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725345703","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725345702"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725346347","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725346347"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDALO"," userResponse":" NDALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725349252","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725349252"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725350050","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725350049"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725351111","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725351110"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEMFUGA"," userResponse":" AMEMFUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725351707","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725351707"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725351712","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725351712"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725352385","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725352384"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725353449","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725353449"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEITWA"," userResponse":" ANAYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725354119","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725354118"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725357097","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725357096"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725358078","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725358078"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725358540","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725358540"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725359151","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725359151"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725359693","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725359693"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725360297","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725360296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725363427","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725363427"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725364340","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725364339"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725365518","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725365518"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMPA"," userResponse":" TUNAMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725366331","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725366330"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFAKA"," userResponse":" NAFAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725369223","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725369220"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725369765","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725369765"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725370332","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725370331"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725370799","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725370799"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725371693","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725371692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725374753","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725374752"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725375953","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725375953"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725376588","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725376588"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725380583","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725380583"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMTUNZA"," userResponse":" TUNAMTUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725381406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725381406"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725381845","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725381845"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725383448","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725383448"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" ANATUSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725386887","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725386886"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUPA"," userResponse":" ANATUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725387884","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725387883"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725389105","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725389105"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725391971","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725391971"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725392522","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725392522"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725393378","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725393378"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUUZA"," userResponse":" HUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725394191","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725394191"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725394295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725394295"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725395163","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725395163"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725395942","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725395941"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725397245","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725397244"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNINUNULIA"," userResponse":" KUNINUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725397989","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725397989"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" VITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725398303","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725398302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725399196","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725399196"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725401905","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725401905"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725402798","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725402797"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725403594","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725403594"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725404436","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725404436"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725407403","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725407403"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725409048","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725409047"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEFAHAMU"," userResponse":" UMEFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725409351","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725409351"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725409926","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725409926"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725411087","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725411087"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725411591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725411590"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725411612","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725411611"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725412067","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725412066"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725412801","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725412801"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725415505","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725415504"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725415628","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725415628"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725421624","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725421624"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SD_OFF1_DES.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725426747","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725426746"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725432159","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725432159"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 7575aee9-2e82-46c8-a95e-bb6cff7cc948"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725441302","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725441302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725442075","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725442074"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMOJA"," userResponse":" KIMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725442934","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725442932"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725443657","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725443656"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725443878","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725443878"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725444569","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725444568"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725445328","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725445327"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji kimoja kilikuwa karibu na msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725448497","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725448497"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725449048","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725449048"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725449820","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725449819"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725450070","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725450069"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725450810","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725450809"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725453746","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725453745"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725454587","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725454586"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725455402","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725455402"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILIWA"," userResponse":" WALILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725455579","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725455579"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725456343","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725456343"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengi waliliwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725459843","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725459843"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725460687","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725460686"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONYWA"," userResponse":" ALIONYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725460875","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725460875"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725461803","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725461802"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725462854","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725462854"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIINGIE"," userResponse":" ASIINGIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725463829","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725463829"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725466989","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725466989"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725468312","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725468312"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPUUZA"," userResponse":" ALIPUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725469036","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725469036"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USHAURI"," userResponse":" USHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725469248","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725469248"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725469948","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725469948"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725473071","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725473070"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725473579","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725473579"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725474436","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725474436"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725475419","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725475419"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja akaenda msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725478467","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725478466"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725479579","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725479579"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725479799","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725479799"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725480363","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725480363"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo alikutana na jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725483941","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725483941"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" ALIMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725484954","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725484954"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725485058","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725485057"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725485600","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725485600"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpeleka katikati ya msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725489150","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725489149"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAMIWA"," userResponse":" ALIVAMIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725489318","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725489318"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725490062","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725490062"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725491071","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725491071"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivamiwa na majitu wakamla."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMLA"," userResponse":" WAKAMLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725494294","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725494294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725495089","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725495088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725496239","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725496239"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake walienda kumtafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUMTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725499415","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725499414"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725500088","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725500088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725501523","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725501522"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725502037","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725502036"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725503099","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725503098"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EKENO"," userResponse":" EKENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725503971","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725503971"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725504929","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725504929"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani mmoja aliwaelekeza kuwa Ekeno aliingia msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725508552","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725508552"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMINI"," userResponse":" WALIAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725509170","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725509170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725509875","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725509874"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELIWA"," userResponse":" AMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725510075","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725510075"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725510670","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725510670"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725513375","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725513374"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725513497","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725513497"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725519271","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725519270"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725525145","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725525145"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725530302","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725530301"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 6222f85e-ded6-441c-a699-6fdbe22f5bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725539481","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725539480"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725539935","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725539935"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725540298","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725540297"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725541061","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725541060"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725541603","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725541603"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725542086","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725542085"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725545202","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725545202"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725545830","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725545830"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725546539","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725546539"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725546738","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725546738"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725547188","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725547187"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725547426","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725547426"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725547932","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725547930"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725548906","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725548906"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725552231","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725552230"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAHITAJI"," userResponse":" NAHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725552771","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725552771"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TONE"," userResponse":" TONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725552947","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725552947"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725553602","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725553602"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725554206","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725554206"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725554546","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725554546"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725555374","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725555374"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINATOKA"," userResponse":" LINATOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725555881","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725555881"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725556494","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725556494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725559721","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725559721"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725560216","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725560216"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725560881","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725560881"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMANDE"," userResponse":" UMANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725561610","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725561610"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725562463","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725562463"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEKAUKA"," userResponse":" UMEKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725565906","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725565906"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISIPOKUNYWA"," userResponse":" NISIPOKUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725566605","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725566605"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725568119","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725568119"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUFA"," userResponse":" NITAKUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725569359","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725569358"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725569817","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725569816"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725570496","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725570495"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725573470","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725573470"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725574056","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725574056"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" NIENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725574508","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725574508"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725575047","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725575047"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725575625","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725575624"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAO"," userResponse":" AMBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725576510","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725576510"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKIA"," userResponse":" NILISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725576954","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725576954"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725577385","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725577384"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725580940","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725580939"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725582671","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725582671"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKUFAGILIA"," userResponse":" UTAKUFAGILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725583436","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725583436"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725584262","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725584262"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725584838","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725584838"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725585292","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725585292"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725585901","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725585900"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEKIMA"," userResponse":" HEKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725587121","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725587120"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONYA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725590142","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725590142"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725590677","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725590677"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725591228","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725591228"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725591787","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725591786"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725591981","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725591981"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725592539","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725592539"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" KIU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725593453","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725593453"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725596653","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725596653"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUFA"," userResponse":" NITAKUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725597501","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725597501"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725598256","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725598256"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITIKUNYWA"," userResponse":" SITIKUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725598879","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725598879"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725599743","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725599742"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOYOTE"," userResponse":" YOYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725603202","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725603202"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725603915","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725603915"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725604647","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725604647"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725605781","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725605781"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725606384","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725606383"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725609232","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725609232"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPITA"," userResponse":" KUPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725609710","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725609710"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725610312","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725610312"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725611673","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725611672"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOKAUKA"," userResponse":" ZILIZOKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725612131","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725612131"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725612519","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725612519"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725613423","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725613423"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725614651","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725614650"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIYOKAUKA"," userResponse":" YALIYOKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725617666","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725617665"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725618550","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725618550"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725619288","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725619288"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWIMBI"," userResponse":" MAWIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725619372","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725619372"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725619881","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725619881"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725621309","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725621309"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKINGURUMA"," userResponse":" YAKINGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725624454","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725624454"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725624981","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725624981"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725625974","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725625974"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUNYWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725626591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725626590"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725627497","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725627497"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725631630","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725631630"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725632470","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725632470"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725633389","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725633389"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIASI"," userResponse":" KIASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725633589","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725633589"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725634144","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725634144"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725635184","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725635184"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUONA"," userResponse":" HAKUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725635589","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725635589"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBI"," userResponse":" WIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725636253","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725636253"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725636822","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725636822"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIJA"," userResponse":" LIKIJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725639949","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725639949"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725640894","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725640893"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJARIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725641564","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725641564"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHIKA"," userResponse":" KUSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725642073","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725642073"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725642691","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725642691"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725644168","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725644168"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOMPITA"," userResponse":" ZILIZOMPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725645149","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725645149"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKIELEA"," userResponse":" ZIKIELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725647901","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725647901"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725649006","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725649006"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFAGILIWA"," userResponse":" ALIFAGILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725649813","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725649812"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725650019","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725650019"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725650487","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725650487"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725653441","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725653441"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725654497","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725654497"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANISAIDIE"," userResponse":" ANISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725657851","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725657851"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" NISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725658735","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725658735"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725662718","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725662718"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725663431","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725663431"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANDA"," userResponse":" PANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725663855","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725663854"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725664819","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725664819"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725665412","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725665412"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEUPE"," userResponse":" MWEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725666226","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725666226"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725666851","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725666851"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725667474","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725667474"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725668512","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725668512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEMNYOSHEA"," userResponse":" AMEMNYOSHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725669230","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725669230"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725669801","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725669801"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725670296","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725670296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725670710","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725670709"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725686381","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725686381"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725686481","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725686480"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725693506","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725693506"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.mc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725701307","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725701307"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 5cf9afdf-b665-4492-894f-2ea31f73d29a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725712393","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725712392"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haraka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725716075","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725716074"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haraka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725717667","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725717667"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725726381","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725726381"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725727957","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725727957"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725733813","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725733812"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725735379","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725735379"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725740076","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725740076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725741642","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725741642"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725748470","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725748470"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725749481","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725749481"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725750026","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725750025"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725761224","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725761223"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725761400","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725761400"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725766885","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725766885"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725774445","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725774445"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725781359","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725781358"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725794211","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725794211"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543725800212","data":{"timestamp":" 1543725800212"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" c60cca0b-c420-41be-b569-af555e879160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543726188900","data":{"timestamp":" 1543726188900"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" aa99697f-faac-4cd1-8731-773dc9a77915"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733456842","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733456842"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" aa99697f-faac-4cd1-8731-773dc9a77915"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733476899","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733476898"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" aa99697f-faac-4cd1-8731-773dc9a77915"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733488897","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733488896"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733489277","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733489277"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733489774","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733489773"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733490131","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733490131"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733490545","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733490545"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733491033","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733491032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733491271","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733491271"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733494490","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733494489"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733494530","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733494529"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733495262","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733495261"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733495655","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733495655"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733495959","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733495957"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733496164","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733496163"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733496372","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733496372"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733496700","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733496699"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733496928","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733496928"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733500052","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733500052"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733500471","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733500471"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733503005","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733503004"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733503208","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733503208"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733503410","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733503410"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733506914","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733506912"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733510687","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733510686"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733511709","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733511709"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733514423","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733514422"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733514800","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733514800"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733515291","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733515290"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733515644","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733515644"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733516049","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733516049"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733516529","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733516528"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733516765","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733516765"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733518588","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733518588"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733518680","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733518680"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 422e185c-a1e4-4690-9f28-01c7f4bd8ac1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733529856","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733529856"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 9d5699fc-a0da-43b6-bad7-90330f2346ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-3-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733536489","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733536488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 9d5699fc-a0da-43b6-bad7-90330f2346ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-3-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733543656","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733543656"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 9d5699fc-a0da-43b6-bad7-90330f2346ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-6-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733549326","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733549326"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 9d5699fc-a0da-43b6-bad7-90330f2346ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733551530","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733551530"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 9d5699fc-a0da-43b6-bad7-90330f2346ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733558988","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733558988"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 9d5699fc-a0da-43b6-bad7-90330f2346ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733569127","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733569127"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_071527"," gameId":" 9d5699fc-a0da-43b6-bad7-90330f2346ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}